[RAJESH CLEARS THROAT]
(Raj:)Go ahead.
(Man on Screen:)Greetings from Mumbai.
I'm Raj's attorney,
Venkatesh Koothrappali.
(Raj:)Also my cousin.
(Howard:)-You brought a lawyer?
-Don't answer that.
(Venkatesh:)I'll get straight to the point.
(Venkatesh:)My client's prepared to surrender
any interest in the ring...
(Venkatesh:)...in exchange for two Kawasaki Jet Skis.
(Leonard:)We're not giving him two Jet Skis.
(Venkatesh:)Look, we're big boys. Why don't we just
cut to the chase and meet in the middle?
(Venkatesh:)One Kawasaki Jet Ski. Done and done.
(Leonard:)No Jet Skis.
(Venkatesh:)All right, forget the Jet Skis.
Forget the Jet Skis? What happened to
"tear them a new one"?
(Venkatesh:)What can I say?
They played hardball. We lost.
(Raj:)-You're useless.
-I told you that when you hired me.
RAJESH: I'm signing off now.
-Call your mother. She worries.
(Howard:)So you know, if we're bringing
in cousins who are lawyers...